You want all my love and my devotion
You want my loving soul right on the line
I have no doubt that I could love you forever
The only trouble is you really don't have the time
You've got one night only, one night only, that's all you have to spare
One night only, let's not pretend to care
One night only, one night only, come on big baby come on
One night only, we only have til dawn
In the morning this feeling will be gone
It has no chance going on
Something so right has got no chance to live
So let's forget about chances, its one night I will give
One night only, one night only,you'll be the only one
One night only then you have to run
one night only, one night only.
there's nothing more to say
one night only, what's getting in the way
one night only, one night only,one night only
end